ABOUT ME

I'm 24 years old, and I live in the Autonomous City of Buenos Aires. I consider myself a calm, detailoriented person with many interests. I have a very creative mind, and although I am persevering, I am also a patient person who prioritizes selfdevelopment.

CONTACT



Manuel Zarraga | LinkedIn



manuzarraga@hotmail.com



ManukBASS (Manu Zarraga)



https://manuzarraga.dev.ar/

STRENGTHS

- Creative
- Time Management
- Attention to Detail
- Self-Development
- Listening Skills
- Patient
- Persevering

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Advanced

Italian: Basic

MANUEL ZARRAGA

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

DataRacing

Freelance Frontend (March 2024, 1 month duration)

- Car search engine design for the page
- Logic to search using filters
- DOM management to display the data obtained

Pawtrics Software

Developer (October 2023 - Present) Intern (May 2023 - October 2023)

- Layout and development of visual components
- Database Integration with Supabase
- · Fetching data in tables for the user

EDUCATION

2022 - 2024 Digital House

Certified Tech Developer

- Front-End Specialization
- Intermediate Title "Professional Developer"

2022

Centro e-Learning UTN

"Initial Web Programmer" Course

2021 - 2022 Platzi

Basic Python Course

2011 - 2016 Instituto María Auxiliadora

High School Diploma

SKILLS AND TOOLS

- · Leadership Abilities
- Proactive and Proficient
- Teamwork
- Effective Communication
- Dedicated and Committed
- Problem Solving
- Analytical and Critical Thinking
- Stress Management
- Organized
- Adaptability

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- React
- Sass
- Material UI
- Git
- Java
- MySQL
- Mailchimp
- Figma